question_data = [
        {"type": "boolean",
         "difficulty": "easy",
         "category": "Entertainment: Film",
         "question": "Brandon Routh plays the titular character in the movie &quot;John Wick&quot;.",
         "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
         "question": "In the original Star Wars trilogy, David Prowse was the actor who physically portrayed Darth Vader.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
         "question": "Leonardo DiCaprio won an Oscar for Best Actor in 2004&#039;s &quot;The Aviator&quot;.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
         "question": "Ewan McGregor did not know the name of the second prequel film of Star Wars during and after filming.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
         "question": "The film &quot;2001: A Space Odyssey&quot; was released on December 31st, 2000.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
         "question": "&quot;Minions&quot; was released on the June 10th, 2015.", "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
         "question": "Samuel L. Jackson had the words, &#039;Bad Motherf*cker&#039; in-scripted on his lightsaber during the filming of Star Wars.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
         "question": "Matt Damon played an astronaut stranded on an extraterrestrial planet in both of the movies Interstellar and The Martian.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
         "question": "Actor Tommy Chong served prison time.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
         "question": "The movie &quot;The Nightmare before Christmas&quot; was all done with physical objects.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
         "question": "In the movie The Revenant, DiCaprio&#039;s character hunts down the killer of his son.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
         "question": "In the original Star Wars trilogy, Alec Guinness provided the voice for Darth Vader.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]
